<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on CS&amp;SS/STAT 564: Bayesian Statistics for the Social Sciences</title>
    <link>/2018/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on CS&amp;SS/STAT 564: Bayesian Statistics for the Social Sciences</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/2018/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CHANGELOG</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/changelog/</guid>
      <description> See the GitHub repository the history of changes.
2018-03-08  Initial draft of syllabus page  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Help with R</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/help/</guid>
      <description>A good place to start is Rstudio’s guide for getting help with R
Asking for Help When asking for help with R it is important to at least
Include the exact code that you ran The error message that you got  Without the code and the error message it can be hard to impossible to diagnose the problem and provide a solution. Questions such as “This isn’t working” or even “I’m getting this error message” aren’t useful without the code and error message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git and GitHub</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/git/</guid>
      <description>What is Git? Git is software for version control (keeping track of the changes and history of files).
 What is GitHub? GitHub is a website that hosts git repositories. It also has tools to enable collaboration on software using git.
 Getting Started with Git RStudio includes a GUI interface to git, which will cover almost all the cases you will encounter in this course. For quick introduction on learn how to use Version control within RStudio, I suggest the “Version Control” chapter of the Working with the RStudio IDE (Part 2) DataCamp course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing R</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/install/</guid>
      <description>Installing or Updating R Install R The R website is … special. Since you probably don’t know or care what a mirror is, here are links to the
 Go to the R Project website Choose the Download and install R your operation system:  Mac: Download R-3.4.3.pkg Windows: First click on base and then on Download R 3.4.3 for Windows    Upgrade R If you already have R installed, to check that you have the newest version of R, run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onboarding Instructions for CS&amp;SS 564, Spring 2018</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Please complete the following before the first day of class (Tuesday, March 27, 2018).
Sign up for our Slack worplace, https://uwcsss564.slack.com. We will use this for announcments, and asking and answering questions in this course. You should have received an invite. If not email the instructors to receive one.
 Sign into the course Slack workplace https://uwcsss564.slack.com, and leave a message on the #onboarding channel. In the message introduce yourself, explain why you are taking this course, and what you hope to get out of taking this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/references/</guid>
      <description>Articles and books references in this course. Download these references as bibtex file here.
Aguilar, Omar, and Mike West. 2000. “Bayesian Dynamic Factor Models and Portfolio Allocation.” Journal of Business &amp;amp; Economic Statistics 18 (3). Informa UK Limited: 338–57. doi:10.1080/07350015.2000.10524875.
 Aitkin, M., and N. Longford. 1986. “Statistical Modelling Issues in School Effectiveness Studies.” Journal of the Royal Statistical Society. Series A (General) 149 (1). [Royal Statistical Society, Wiley]: 1–43. http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>