<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Assignments on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</title>
    <link>/2018/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Assignments on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/2018/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposal</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/1-project-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/1-project-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Add the file doc/initial-proposal.md In a paragraph or two:
State a research question. Describe what data you will use to answer the question. Discuss where and how will you get that data.  Commit changes to GitHub. We will do this at the start of class
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposal II</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/2-project-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/2-project-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Instructions Add a Markdown or R Markdown file in your named doc/initial-proposal.md to your project repository. Answer the questions in the next section in that file. To submit the assignment,
 Commit and push all changes GitHub Open an issue in your project repository Title it “Review Project Proposal II” Assign the issue to @jrnold and @calvinhgarner Submit the issue
  See the Project Workflow.
 Proposal In one to two paragraphs propose a research project for this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis I (Data Wrangling and EDA)</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/3-project-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/3-project-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Exact instructions of directory organization to follow.
The purpose of this assignment is to encourage you to find, load, clean, and explore your data before continuing to analysis.
State your research question, and your expected research design to answer that question. What are your data sources? Cite the data appropriately using name or title of the data set, authors, version, creation date, and persistent data identifier (e.g. DOI) if available or URL if one is not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis 2</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/4-project-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/4-project-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Write this asisgnment in a file named data-analysis-2.Rmd in your repository. It may-be useful to copy material the previous assignment as a starting point since this should be viewed as a draft towards your final project.
To submit this assignment:
Open a pull request titled “Review Data Analysis 2” Assign it to @jrnold and @CalvinGarner See the instructions on what to include in the comment.  Instructions This assignment should be viewed as a step towards producing a final project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draft</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/5-project-assignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/5-project-assignment/</guid>
      <description>Address theoretical, data, and methodological issues from the previous data analysis assignments.
At this stage, your data wrangling should be complete, and that section should be mostly written.
In this draft you should make some attempt at analysis that answers your research question. Consider the following.
Is it a causal question? What is the identification strategy? What assumptions are being made, and are they plausible? Is it a predictive question? How are your measuring predictive performance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>/2018/projects/final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/final-project/</guid>
      <description>Answer a research question using the statistical and computational methods used in this course. It can be a descriptive, predictive, or causal question. What is important for this reports is that the question and stated clearly, the methods and data used to answer the question are described clearly, and a discussion of why the methods and data used to answer the question are appropriate, and a discusison of th assumptions made by those methods and the limits of what we can learn from this research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/2018/projects/_book/instructions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/_book/instructions/</guid>
      <description>Proposal    1 Instructions 2 Proposal 2.1 Instructions      Proposal   Proposal  1 Instructions Add a Markdown or R Markdown file in your named doc/initial-proposal.md to your project repository. Answer the questions in the next section in that file. To submit the assignment,
 Commit and push all changes GitHub Open an issue in your project repository Title it “Review Project Proposal II” Assign the issue to @jrnold and @calvinhgarner Submit the issue</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/2018/projects/_book/proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/projects/_book/proposal/</guid>
      <description>Proposal    1 Instructions 2 Proposal 2.1 Instructions      Proposal   2 Proposal In one to two paragraphs propose a research project for this course. State your research question. Describe what data you will be using to address that question.
Address any comments from the first proposal. What is your research question or puzzle? If you have a clear question: is it descriptive, predictive, or causal (or some combination of them).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>