<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>POLS/CS&amp;SS 503 (Spring 2018) on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</title>
    <link>/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in POLS/CS&amp;SS 503 (Spring 2018) on POLS 503: Advanced Quantitative Political Methodology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CHANGELOG</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/changelog/</guid>
      <description> See the GitHub repository the history of changes.
2018-03-08  Initial draft of syllabus page  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Help with R</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/help/</guid>
      <description>A good place to start is Rstudio’s guide for getting help with R
Asking for Help When asking for help with R it is important to at least
Include the exact code that you ran The error message that you got  Without the code and the error message it can be hard to impossible to diagnose the problem and provide a solution. Questions such as “This isn’t working” or even “I’m getting this error message” aren’t useful without the code and error message.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git and GitHub</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/git/</guid>
      <description>For quick introduction on learn how to use Version control within RStudio, I suggest the “Version Control” chapter of the Working with the RStudio IDE (Part 2) DataCamp course.
Relationship between GitHub and Local Git Projects  References  Jenny Bryan, Happy Git and GitHub for the useR DataCamp course Version Control with Git. This course requires shell knowledge, but the following two modules are useful.  Automated Version Control Using Git from RStudio  Simple guide to forks in GitHub and Git GitHub Help Git and GitHub videos for beginners from dataschool introduces git and GitHub via many videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git: Assignment Submission and Workflow</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/git-assignment-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/git-assignment-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Cloning, Pull Requests, Forking, Pulling, and Pushing See the Happy Git and GitHub for the useR chapter Fork a repo.
 Instructions Go to the course website, click Assignments.
 Scroll down to the Assignments section, click on the link to the assignment under Instructions and Submissions.
 Click on the Fork button to fork the repository to your GitHub account.
 Click Clone or download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git: Project Submission and Workflow</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/git-project-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/git-project-workflow/</guid>
      <description>For the project assignments, each student has a repository named UW-POLS501/:username where :username is the GitHub username of the student. This does not need to be forked. The student works directly on that repository, and submits assignments by opening an issue on UW-POLS501/:username/issue.
 {&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;diagram&#34;:&#34;sequenceDiagram\n participant remote as UW-POLS501/student\n participant local as local repository\n remote-local: Clone repository\n Note over remote: Assignment 1\n loop Until completed\n local-local: Work and commit\n local-remote: Push changes\n end\n remote-remote: Open issue to submit\n Note over remote: Assignment 2\n loop Until completed\n local-local: Work and commit\n local-remote: Push changes\n end\n remote-remote: Open issue to submit&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing R</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/install/</guid>
      <description>Installing or Updating R Install R The R website is … special. Since you probably don’t know or care what a mirror is, here are links to the
 Go to the R Project website Choose the Download and install R your operation system:  Mac: Download R-3.4.3.pkg Windows: First click on base and then on Download R 3.4.3 for Windows    Upgrade R If you already have R installed, to check that you have the newest version of R, run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on R for Data Science</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/r4ds-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/r4ds-notes/</guid>
      <description>Visualization Other resources:
 All the graph things Stat 545. Jenny Bryan.   Tibbles Why might you want to create non-syntactic variable names? Since variable names are often used as in plots (e.g. axis-titles) or headers in tables, where having spaces or other characters that are invalid R variable names is useful. Those functions will have ways to use text other than the column, but using the non-syntactic variable name can be convenient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onboarding</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Please complete the following before the first day of class.
 Sign up for our Slack channel. You should have received an invite. If not email the instructors. Sign up for a GitHub Fill out course survey using the course. The should have received an email with the link. A link is also posted on the Slack channel. Fill out the survey with office hour preferences. See the email sent to the class or the Slack channel for a link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>/2018/pages/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/pages/references/</guid>
      <description>Articles and books references in this course. Download these references as bibtex file here.
Angrist, Joshua D, and Jörn-Steffen Pischke. 2010. “The Credibility Revolution in Empirical Economics: How Better Research Design Is Taking the Con Out of Econometrics.” Journal of Economic Perspectives 24 (2). American Economic Association: 3–30. doi:10.1257/jep.24.2.3.
 Bailey, Michael A., Anton Strezhnev, and Erik Voeten. 2016. “Estimating Dynamic State Preferences from United Nations Voting Data.” Journal of Conflict Resolution 61 (2).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>